Hey hey hey hey hey hey (hoo hoo)
1990’s (how we do it)
Some things last forever (they say)
Katanya ada hal-hal yang abadi (they say)
永遠なものがあるって (they say)
Dicen que algunas cosas son eternas (they say)
อาจจะมีบางอย่างที่อยู่ชั่วนิรันดร์ (they say)
世上存在永恒的东西 (they say)
Có những thứ là mãi mãi (they say)
We like to keep it cool (our way)
Kami suka sesuatu yang keren (our way)
僕らはクールなものが好き (our way)
A nosotros nos gusta lo que es cool (our way)
เราชอบอะไรคูลๆ (our way)
我们喜欢炫酷的东西 (our way)
Chúng ta thích những thứ hay ho (our way)
Now, who’s the hottest? (boy)
Ayo siapa saja yang seksi? (boy)
さぁ、誰がホットだって？ (boy)
Bien, ¿quiénes son los que son hot? (boy)
แล้วตอนนี้ใครฮ็อตที่สุด? (boy)
说谁火来着? (boy)
Chà bây giờ xem ai hot hơn? (boy)
Can you feel this too? (how we do it)
Kau pun merasakannya bukan? (how we do it)
君も感じるだろう (how we do it)
Tú lo sientes también (how we do it)
เธอเองก็รู้สึกใช่ไหม (how we do it)
你也感受到了吧 (how we do it)
Bạn cũng thấy vậy phải không? (how we do it)
This is an old school vibe (that vibe)
Suasana ini old school vibe (that vibe)
この雰囲気はOld school vibe (that vibe)
Esta onda es old school vibe (that vibe)
บรรยากาศย้อนวัย vibe (that vibe)
这个气氛是old school vibe (that vibe)
Bầu không khí Old School vibe này (that vibe)
Singing along kids on the block (on the block)
Bernyanyi bersama kids on the block (on the block)
真似て歌う kids on the block (on the block)
Cantando juntos kids on the block (on the block)
ร้องเพลงตามกันไป kids on the block (on the block)
跟着唱的kids on the block (on the block)
những đứa trẻ hát theo kids on the block (on the block)
Boombox rockin' the alley make some noise
Boombox yang mengguncang jalanan, teriakkan suaranya
路地を揺らす boombox 叫べ
Sacudiendo callejones boombox A gritar
ตะโกนเสียง boombox เขย่าซอย
响彻胡同的boombox 呐喊起来
Boombox khuấy đảo con hẻm này, hãy hét lên
見たことない時間の意味
ความหมายของช่วงเวลาที่ไม่เคยพบเจอ
Ý nghĩa của quãng thời gian chưa từng trải qua
The meaning of time I’ve never seen
Arti waktu yang tak terlihat
Lo que significa un tiempo que nunca he visto
未曾见证的时间的意义
I walk along the orange Apgujeong street
Melangkah melewati sinar oranye Apgujeong
オレンジの狎鴎亭(アックジョン)を歩く
Caminando por la naranja Apgujeong
เดินตามถนน Apgujeong ใต้แสงไฟสีส้ม
走在橙光笼罩下的狎鸥亭
Rảo bước trên con phố Apgujeong đầy ánh sắc cam
If you feel this too, come and find me
Jika kau merasakannya juga, come and find me
君も感じているなら come and find me
Si tú también lo sientes come and find me
ถ้าเธอเองก็รู้สึก come and find me
如果你也感受到 come and find me
Nếu bạn cũng chung cảm giác này, come and find me
This world is moving again
Dunia ini sedang berputar
这世界又开始动摇
この世界はまた動いている
Este mundo se mueve otra vez
โลกนี้กำลังเคลื่อนไหวอีกครั้ง
Thế giới này vẫn luôn xoay chuyển
Take it out take it out
Coba keluarkan keluarkan
取り出して 取り出して
Sácalo, prueba y
เอาออกมา เอาออกมา เอาออกมา it’s fun
拿出来 拿出来
Bỏ đi, bỏ đi,
Take it out take it out it’s fun
Coba keluarkan it's fun
取り出して 取り出して it’s fun
Sácalo prueba y sácalo it’s fun
拿出来 拿出来 it’s fun
Bỏ đi, bỏ đi it's fun
You and I here
Di sini kau dan aku
ここに君と僕
Aquí tú y yo
เธอและฉันที่อยู่ตรงนี้
这里你和我
Nơi đây, bạn và tôi
With your and my style
Dengan gayaku dan gayamu saja
君と僕だけのスタイルで
Al estilo tuyo y mío
ปล่อยไปตามสไตล์ของเธอและฉัน
你和我的专属风格
Phong cách của riêng bạn và tôi
(Let’s show off like the 90’s)
(Bertindak angkuh sepuasnya like the 90's)
(思いきり胸を張ってみよう like the 90’s)
(A presumir todo lo que quieras like the 90’s)
(แสดงออกมาให้เต็มที่ like the 90’s)
(尽情炫耀吧 like the 90’s)
(Cứ thoải mái ra vẻ ta đây đi like the 90's)
This is how we do it everything here
This is how we do it semua di sini
This is how we do it すべてここに
This is how we do it Todos aquí
This is how we do it ทั้งหมดที่นี่
This is how we do it 都在这里
This is how we do it mọi thứ ở ngay đây
Woo what you waitin’ for
Bring a new romance
Membawa romansa baru
新しいロマンを呼び出して
A evocar un nuevo romance
เรียกความฝันครั้งใหม่ออกมา
唤起新的浪漫
Mang đến sự lãng mạn mới
Woo we about to go
We want
Kita ingin
僕らは望んでいる
Nosotros queremos
เราต้องการ
我们想要
Chúng ta đều muốn
Here we go here we go here we go ay
(เราต้องการ)
(We want)
(Kita ingin)
(我们想要)
(僕らは望んでいる)
(Chúng ta đều muốn)
(Nosotros queremos)
We want
Kita ingin
僕らは望んでいる
Nosotros queremos
เราต้องการ
我们想要
Chúng ta đều muốn
Here we go here we go here we go oh
That 90’s love
Don’t this hit really feeling like jump jump
Don’t this hit rasa yang sungguh seperti jump jump
Don’t this hit 很有感觉的jump jump
Don’t this hit 本当にいい感じの jump jump
Don’t this hit Se siente de verdad jump jump
Don’t this hit ความรู้สึกกำลังมา jump jump
Don’t this hit cảm giác thật đã đến jump jump
Don’t this hit mood ของเรา
Don’t this hit this is our mood
Don’t this hit ini hanya milik kita mood
Don’t this hit これは僕らだけの mood
Don’t this hit Esto es solo nuestro mood
Don’t this hit 这是我们专属的mood
Don’t this hit đây là mood của riêng chúng ta
Don’t this hit really feeling like jump jump
Don’t this hit rasa yang sungguh seperti jump jump
Don’t this hit 本当にいい感じの jump jump
Don’t this hit Se siente de verdad jump jump
Don’t this hit ความรู้สึก jump jump
Don’t this hit 很有感觉的jump jump
Don’t this hit cảm giác thật đã đến jump jump
Don't this
The street wear that swept across the block
Menyapu jalan sepanjang street
道を掃いて回ったストリート
Barriendo las calles street
ถนนที่ถูกกวาดเรียบไปทุกเส้นทาง
横扫大街小巷的街头风
Thời trang đường phố quét khắp nẻo đường
Now it’s just a classic (blow that)
Sekarang hanya klasik (blow that)
今はただのクラシック (blow that)
Ahora ya es un clásico (blow that)
จากนี้มีแค่ความคลาสสิก (blow that)
现在只是经典 (blow that)
Giờ thì là cổ điển (blow that)
My pocket was loose (I show that)
Kantong yang longgar (I show that)
ポケットはダボダボだった (I show that)
Los bolsillos grandes (I show that)
กระเป๋าที่หลวม (I show that)
口袋松松垮垮 (I show that)
Cháy túi rồi chứ gì? (I show that)
A tomar la foto cheese (clack)
Nào chụp ảnh đi cheese (clack)
さぁ 撮って cheese (clack)
Now, let’s shoot, cheese (clack)
Ayo foto cheese (clack)
ถ่ายรูปกัน cheese (clack)
来 拍吧 cheese (clack)
Friends in the film all make V (you know that)
Semua teman yang ada dalam bingkai make V (you know that)
フィルムの中の友だちみんな make V (you know that)
Los amigos en la cinta todos make V (you know that)
เพื่อนทุกคนในฟิล์มต่าง make V (you know that)
胶卷里的朋友全部make V (you know that)
Bạn bè trong ảnh phim cũng đều make V (you know that)
Let’s go mob your moves stay here yeah
Let’s go mob kemari dengan gerakanmu itu yeah
Let’s go mob 君の動きがそのままここに yeah
Let’s go mob Tu movimiento así aquí yeah
Let’s go mob การเคลื่อนไหวของเธออยู่ตรงนี้ yeah
Let’s go mob 你的动作原封不动到这里 yeahh
Let's go mob hãy cứ chuyển động như vậy đấy yeah
Fresh off Otra vez se calienta new decades
Fresh off กลับมาร้อนแรงอีกครั้ง new decades
Fresh off 再び熱くなった new decades
Fresh off new decades heating up again
Fresh off kembali memanas new decades
Fresh off 重新火热起来的new decades
Fresh off lại hâm nóng new decades
I stay up all night watching ‘Friends’ like my friends
Seperti temanku ‘Friends’ melihatnya sepanjang malam
僕の友達みたいな「Friends」見ながら夜を明かす
Parecen mis amigos ‘Friends’ vemos toda la noche
โต้รุ่งดู ‘Friends’ กับเพื่อนของฉัน
看着如我的朋友般的'Friends’通宵
Cũng thức đêm xem "Friends" cho bằng bạn bằng bè
Maybe we’re on the same parallel line
Mungkin kita berada di parallel yang sama
もしかしたら僕らは同じ平行線の上
Quizás estamos en líneas paralelas estamos
บางทีเราอาจจะอยู่บนเส้นขนานเดียวกัน
或许我们站在同一条平行线上
Có lẽ chúng ta đang trên cùng một đường thẳng song song
Listen, DJ drops it (drop)
Coba dengarkan DJ drops it (drop)
聞いてみて DJ drops it (drop)
Escucha DJ drops it (drop)
ลองฟังสิ DJ drops it (drop)
你听 DJ drops it (drop)
Nghe thử đi DJ drops it (drop)
You can't avoid this feeling
Tak bisa tak merasa
Feelingを感じるしかない
Solo lo puedes sentir
เทอไม่สามารถปฏิเสธความรู้สึกนี้ได้
只能感受这份感觉
Các giác quan không ngừng cảm nhận
(feel a way feel a way what)
‘Cause the night is short
Pendeknya malam ini
この夜は短いから
Porque esta noche corta es
เพราะคืนนี้มันสั้น
夜晚转瞬即逝
đêm nay thật ngắn
So let me see you do your thang (come on)
The meaning of a space I’ve never been in
Arti ruang yang tak pernah didatangi
行ったことない空間の意味
Lo que significa un espacio nunca visitado
ความหมายของพื้นที่ที่ไม่เคยเยือน
未曾去过的空间的意义
Ý nghĩa của không gian chưa từng đặt chân đến
We feel each other’s presence 90’s love
Merasakan keberadaan satu sama lain 90's love
互いの存在を感じる 90’s love
Nos sentimos uno al otro 90’s love
สัมผัสถึงการมีอยู่ของกันและกัน 90’s love
感受对方的存在 90’s love
Cảm nhận được sự hiện diện của chúng ta 90's love
When you become stronger, come and find me
Jika kau semakin kuat, come and find me
力が大きくなっていくと come and find me
Cuando se agranda la energía come and find me
ถ้าเธอมีพลังแข็งแกร่งขึ้น come and find me
力量强大之后 come and find me
Khi cảm thấy mạnh mẽ hơn come and find me
Beyond the KWANGYA, come closer
Melewati KWANGYA untuk mendekat
KWANGYAを越えてもっと近くにくる
Más allá de KWANGYA acércate más
ก้าวข้าม KWANGYA ใกล้เข้ามาอีก
越过KWANGYA 更进一步
Vượt qua KWANGYA, tiến đến gần hơn
Take it out take it out
Coba keluarkan keluarkan
取り出して 取り出して
Sácalo, prueba y
เอาออกมา เอาออกมา เอาออกมา it’s fun
拿出来 拿出来
Bỏ đi, bỏ đi,
Take it out take it out it’s fun
Coba keluarkan it's fun
取り出して 取り出して it’s fun
Sácalo prueba y sácalo it’s fun
拿出来 拿出来 it’s fun
Bỏ đi, bỏ đi it's fun
Here you and I
Di sini kau dan aku
ここに君と僕
Aquí tú y yo
เธอและฉันที่อยู่ตรงนี้
这里你和我
Nơi đây, bạn và tôi
With you and my style
Dengan gayaku dan gayamu saja
君と僕だけのスタイルで
Al estilo tuyo y mío
สไตล์ของเธอและฉัน
你和我的专属风格
Phong cách của riêng bạn và tôi
That's who we are, put it down like that
Itu adalah kita put it down like that
それがまさに僕らなんだ put it down like that
Eso somos nosotros put it down like that
นี่แหละคือเรา put it down like that
那就是我们 put it down like that
đó mới là chúng ta put it down like that
(Let’s show off like the 90’s)
(Bertindak angkuh sepuasnya like the 90's)
(思いきり胸を張ってみよう like the 90’s)
(A presumir todo lo que quieras like the 90’s)
(โชว์ออกมาให้เต็มที่ like the 90’s)
(尽情炫耀吧 like the 90’s)
(Cứ thoải mái ra vẻ ta đây đi like the 90's)
This is how we do it everything here
This is how we do it semua di sini
This is how we do it すべてここに
This is how we do it Todos aquí
This is how we do it ทั้งหมดที่นี่
This is how we do it 都在这里
This is how we do it mọi thứ ở ngay đây
Woo what you waitin’ for
Bring a new romance
Membawa romansa baru
新しいロマンを呼び出して
A evocar un nuevo romance
เรียกความฝันครั้งใหม่ออกมา
唤起新的浪漫
Mang đến sự lãng mạn mới
Woo we about to go
We want
Kita ingin
僕らは望んでいる
Nosotros queremos
เราต้องการ
我们想要
Chúng ta đều muốn
Here we go here we go here we go ay
(We want)
(Kita ingin)
(僕らは望んでいる)
(Nosotros queremos)
(เราต้องการ)
(我们想要)
(Chúng ta đều muốn)
We want
Kita ingin
僕らは望んでいる
Nosotros queremos
เราต้องการ
我们想要
Chúng ta đều muốn
Here we go here we go here we go oh
That 90’s love
Don’t this hit really feeling like
Don’t this hit rasa yang sungguh seperti jump jump
Don't this hit 本当にいい感じの
Don’t this hit Se siente de verdad
Don’t this hit ความรู้สึกกำลังมา
Don't this hit 很有感觉的
Don’t this hit cảm giác thật đã đến
Tonight the new clash
Tonight tumbukan yang baru itu
Tonight 新しいその衝突
Tonight Ese choque nuevo
Tonight การปะทะครั้งใหม่
Tonight 一场新的冲突
Tonight làn sóng đang lan tỏa
The wave is spreading
Panjang gelombang menyebar
紋は広がっている
Las ondas esparciéndose van
คลื่นกำลังแพร่กระจายไป
风波正在蔓延
sóng va chạm đã lan rộng
(It’s growing yeah)
(Semakin besar yeah)
(大きくなっている yeah)
(Se agrandan yeah)
(กำลังโตขึ้น yeah)
(正在扩大 yeah)
(đang dần lớn hơn nữa yeah)
I felt the KOSMO I could almost reach to
Mungkin kurasakan KOSMO yang bisa kujangkau
もしかしたら届きそうなKOSMOを感じたんだ 僕は
Quizás sentí yo el KOSMO que casi puedo tocar
รู้สึกถึง KOSMO ที่ฉันกำลังจะไปถึง
我感受到了似乎能触及的KOSMO
Dường như tôi đã cảm nhận được KOSMO mà mình sắp chạm đến
Let me show you 90’s love
That’s who we are
Itu adalah kita
それが僕らなんだ
Eso somos nosotros
นี่แหละคือเรา
那就是我们
đó mới là chúng ta
Let me show you 90’s love
This is how we do it everything here
This is how we do it semua di sini
This is how we do it すべてここに
This is how we do it Todos aquí
This is how we do it ทั้งหมดที่นี่
This is how we do it 都在这里
This is how we do it mọi thứ ở ngay đây
Woo what you waitin’ for
Bring a new romance
Membawa romansa baru
新しいロマンを呼び出して
A evocar un nuevo romance
เรียกความฝันครั้งใหม่ออกมา
唤起新的浪漫
Mang đến sự lãng mạn mới
Woo we about to go
We want
Kita ingin
僕らは望んでいる
Nosotros queremos
เราต้องการ
我们想要
Chúng ta đều muốn
Here we go here we go here we go ay
(We want)
(Kita ingin)
(僕らは望んでいる)
(Nosotros queremos)
(เราต้องการ)
(我们想要)
(Chúng ta đều muốn)
We want
Kita ingin
僕らは望んでいる
Nosotros queremos
เราต้องการ
我们想要
Chúng ta đều muốn
Here we go here we go here we go oh
That 90’s love